[
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "On%20a%20London%20Underground%20map%2C%20what%20colour%20is%20the%20Circle%20Line%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Yellow",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Green"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20country%20inside%20the%20United%20Kingdom%20does%20NOT%20appear%20on%20its%20flag%2C%20the%20Union%20Jack%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Wales",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Scotland",
            "Ireland",
            "Isle%20of%20Wight"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20countries%20is%20%22doubly%20landlocked%22%20%28surrounded%20entirely%20by%20one%20or%20more%20landlocked%20countries%29%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Uzbekistan",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Switzerland",
            "Bolivia",
            "Ethiopia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20city%20in%20Saudi%20Arabia%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Dubai",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Riyadh",
            "Mecca",
            "Medina"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Chile%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Santiago",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Valpara%C3%ADso",
            "Copiap%C3%B3",
            "Antofagasta"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20European%20city%20has%20the%20highest%20mileage%20of%20canals%20in%20the%20world%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Birmingham",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Venice",
            "Amsterdam",
            "Berlin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20city%20in%20Morocco%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Casablanca",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Rabat",
            "Fes",
            "Sale"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20are%20the%20four%20corner%20states%20of%20the%20US%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Utah%2C%20Colorado%2C%20Arizona%2C%20New%20Mexico",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Oregon%2C%20Idaho%2C%20Nevada%2C%20Utah",
            "Kansas%2C%20Oklahoma%2C%20Arkansas%2C%20Louisiana",
            "South%20Dakota%2C%20Minnesota%2C%20Nebraska%2C%20Iowa"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20following%20Spanish%20provinces%20are%20located%20in%20the%20northern%20area%20of%20Spain%20except%3A",
        "correct_answer": "Murcia",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Asturias",
            "Navarre",
            "Le%C3%B3n"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20does%20NOT%20recognize%20Armenia%20as%20an%20independent%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Pakistan",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Iran",
            "Turkey",
            "Azerbaijan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "All%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20have%20official%20claims%20to%20territory%20in%20Antartica%20EXCEPT%3A",
        "correct_answer": "United%20States",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Australia",
            "Chile",
            "Norway"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Gibraltar%2C%20located%20just%20south%20of%20the%20Iberian%20peninsula%2C%20is%20a%20territory%20of%20which%20West%20Europe%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "United%20Kingdom",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Spain",
            "Portugal",
            "France"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How%20many%20countries%20are%20larger%20than%20Australia%3F",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "4",
            "3",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20historical%20city%20Timbuktu%20is%20located%20in%20which%20West%20African%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Mali",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Senegal",
            "Niger",
            "Burkina%20Faso"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Senegal%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Dakar",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Nouakchott",
            "Conakry",
            "Monrovia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20right%20way%20to%20spell%20the%20capital%20of%20Hungary%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Budapest",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Boodapest",
            "Bhudapest",
            "Budapast"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20tiny%20principality%20lies%20between%20Spain%20and%20France%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Andorra",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Liechtenstein",
            "Monaco",
            "San%20Marino"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20official%20language%20of%20Bhutan%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Dzongkha",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ladakhi",
            "Karen",
            "Groma"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20country%20has%20three%20capital%20cities%3F",
        "correct_answer": "South%20Africa",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Somalia",
            "China",
            "United%20Kingdom"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20towns%20of%20Brugelette%2C%20Arlon%20and%20Ath%20are%20located%20in%20which%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Belgium",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Andorra",
            "France",
            "Luxembourg"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20smallest%20country%20in%20South%20America%20by%20area%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Suriname",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Brazil",
            "Uruguay",
            "Chile"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20countries%20borders%20with%20Poland%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Lithuania",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "France",
            "Norway",
            "Netherlands"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20land%20mass%20of%20modern%20day%20Turkey%20is%20called%20what%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Anatolia",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ismuth%20of%20Ottoma",
            "Ottoma",
            "Ismuth%20of%20Anatolia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20countries%20is%20the%20smallest%20by%20population%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Norway",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Slovakia",
            "Finland",
            "Hong%20Kong"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20the%202016%20Global%20Peace%20Index%20poll%2C%20out%20of%20163%20countries%2C%20what%20was%20the%20United%20States%20of%20America%20ranked%3F",
        "correct_answer": "103",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "10",
            "59",
            "79"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20highest%20mountain%20in%20the%20world%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Mt.%20Everest",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mount%20Godwin%20Austen",
            "Kangchenjunga",
            "Annapurna"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20region%20conjoining%20Pakistan%2C%20India%2C%20and%20China%20with%20unknown%20leadership%20called%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Kashmir",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Andorra",
            "Gibraltar",
            "Quin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20was%20the%20most%20populous%20city%20in%20the%20Americas%20in%202015%3F",
        "correct_answer": "S%C3%A3o%20Paulo",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "New%20York",
            "Mexico%20City",
            "Los%20Angeles"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Broome%20is%20a%20town%20in%20which%20state%20of%20Australia%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Western%20Australia",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Northern%20Territory",
            "South%20Australia",
            "Tasmania"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Where%20is%20the%20%22Sonoran%20Desert%22%20located%3F",
        "correct_answer": "North%20America",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "South%20America",
            "Asia",
            "Africa"
        ]
    }
]